{
    "id": "377f6bf3e90244d4af47ea1a4dd46625",
    "title": "Enough: grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "25754f9952f54f98b3927535d65a2194",
            "title": "Enough Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I didn’t run ………………….. to catch the bus.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "enough fast",
                        "fast enough"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ………………….. to know better.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "old enough",
                        "enough old"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have bought …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "milk enough",
                        "enough milk"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was ………………… to lock the car.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "enough prudent",
                        "prudent enough"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was ………………… to trust her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "stupid enough",
                        "enough stupid"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Is it ………………… for you?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "enough warm",
                        "warm enough"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have we got ………………… for buying the tickets?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "money enough",
                        "enough money"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Many tablet computers are ………………….. to put in your pocket.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "enough small",
                        "small enough"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We haven’t got ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "chairs enough",
                        "enough chairs"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We haven’t got …………………. paint.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "enough blue",
                        "blue enough"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}